all those there was what I wanted to do
hacker ring it's one of those pretty
Saturday gang oh good I got banned once
again whoo all right No
evidence of that worked
was the programming challenge to get
higher
and this is broken
yeah I'm sorry the ban was too crappy it
was a triple bite
let's go
thank you for subscribing ok
why is caching used to increase your you
performance thank you for subscribing
why do I have internet something
I know
let's try let's try plugging in the wire
nevermind no wires Internet no it's not
it's mine oh well yeah that's broken
a surge wedgie stillness broken today
too slow
I don't know why it's broken let me well
we don't hack things anymore
you're tired
oh so slow let me see if I get here
look what we got we got a wire I know I
know on the fringe being dropped we've
wired now maybe wire will fix
yeah I need a slop okay that looks okay
should be there
let's leave all this crap I don't even
know what it all does
okay
[Music]
oh here a Belkin let's try that one well
there's a USB 2.0 Ethernet adapter it'll
have your less bound
can harm our app system I know I used to
do that to fix my 4chan all the time but
I think it works on Macs
it's not refresh
it's when a USB like broken
okay no those look like the problem here
real tech semiconductor cork so I'll
show up is network and deleted most to
the Hat
no network
is connected but your computer does not
have an IP address
that's it
it's not better
all right we're on wired now let's go Oh
get off her some top tech companies
let's play this game it makes the first
read fat no it make a second and
subsequent reads faster you'll need an
email to save my progress haircut man at
Mill inator calm
what haircut man I'm keeping this a
secret
oh man we've got a phone number 201 nine
eight seven six three three three
position non-engineering oh no
internship full-time engineering how
good eight years full-time I'm a green
card holder within a week never the Bay
Area assure the Bay Area all right
generalist engineering pledge I promise
to answer myself without help from
anyone guys you can hear me okay are we
good are we too laggy should we lower
the bandwidth I'll supply retrieves did
from a table that be select they asked
me this question already maintain the
users logged in states cookies they're
illegal in Europe fill in the missing
line of code if num is greater than max
no max not equals num select the answer
y equals Baz X what is the value of Z
what do you have bar and I'm going to do
have foo to be bar select the line of
code that function that calls this
method on an object you have to push
result array push value element can be
used to obtain the elements of a binary
search tree in sorted order this is
garbage who's heard of any of these
algorithms is this a trick question
function returns index of first matching
element in array
returned
kind of language is this is this like
Ruby return I if array element equals
element sure suppose you're designing a
distributed worker library and would
like to be able to queue jobs what is a
good method of making the code work well
the best way is to write three versions
of the library global function
referential transparency so what just
looks the most correct
and coding is complete you'd like to
update the UI or spinlock so we love
spin locks
sure this is bored I'm bored
okay so Larry gets printed first when
foo is run and then Moe will be printed
and then curly will be printed oh sorry
and I got a op tes this is boring I'm
bored
what should we do let's do something
we're not here to answer that that was
boring
yeah Lao remember the password for
haircut man absolutely
yeah sorry we'll make a bigger no I
don't want to twitch slam I want you
something new can I allow people to talk
on my twitch if you're a subscriber that
kind of be nice wait am I still laggy
this is nevermind I'm done
streaming today this is garbage
someone needs to fix the internet in
this house
know this you have people I was gonna
I'd do it for Pico CT I will see if he
goes ooh Kiev I think they'll be mad at
me I'm friends with these guys I don't
wanna do their things on a live stream
this is
well my friends are just being dropped
periscope to know okay okay okay okay
this is all right
I'm out this is this I gotta get better
internet give me money I'll buy better
Internet